csgoshop.com 2019-09-28

# Privacy Policy | CSGOShop

**OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**

**Last Updated: May 18, 2016**

CSGOShop Ltd. ( **“CSGOShop”, “CSGOShop (Site)”, “we”** or **“us”** ) is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We have developed this privacy policy (the **“Privacy Policy”** ) to protect your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how we gather and use your information and applies to all who use our web site, commerce services, other electronic services or any service CSGOShop makes available to you, or who purchase products provided by CSGOShop (the **“Services”** ), any individual, business partner-specific, merchant-specific, city-specific, or other area-specific web sites we offer that link to or reference this Privacy Policy (collectively, the **“Site”** ) and when you receive electronic communications from us.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and review it periodically for the latest information about our privacy practices. **By using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with your personal information or interact with the Site and/or Services.**

We will routinely update this Privacy Policy to clarify our practices and to reflect new or different privacy practices, such as when we add new services, functionality or features to the Site. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of notice on the Site prior to the change becoming effective. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the date it was “Last Updated” above. If you do not agree to the revised Privacy Policy, please stop using the Site and/or Services.

**_I. THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT_**

We collect only personal information that is relevant and necessary to the purpose of our Site. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We collect the following types of information from our users:

**A. Personally Identifiable Information Collected from Individuals**

We receive and store any information you enter on our Site, or provide to us in any other way, including by e-mail or through a third-party service that you link to your CSGOShop account. When you send an e-mail to CSGOShop, we may retain your e-mail address and the contents of the e-mail you send.

“Personal Identifiable Information” may include, but shall not be limited to, your name, address, and the full bank account number and/or credit card numbers you provide when you use the Services.

**Billing Information** : If you purchase or sell goods or services using the Services, PayPal may collect financial information, such as the full bank account number and/or credit card numbers you provide when you use the Site, make your purchase, or list a product or service for sale using the Services, and such information is subject to PayPal’s privacy policy, which is available [here](https://www.paypal.com/ca/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full). If you purchase products or service, sell products or services, or list products or services for sale using the Services, we may receive from Valve Corporation or Valve S.a.r.l. (collectively “Valve”) Personal Identifiable Information. If you purchase products or services or sell products or services using the Services we may receive from PayPal Personal Identifiable Information. 

**Know Your Client** : By using the Site, you authorise us, directly or indirectly, to make any inquiries we consider necessary to validate your identity. You must, at our request (1) provide further information to us, which may include your date of birth and other information that will allow us to reasonably identify you; (2) take steps to confirm ownership of your email address or financial instruments; and (3) verify your information against third party databases or through other sources. You must also, at our request, provide copies of identification documents (such as your driver’s license). We reserve the right to close, suspend, or limit access to your account, the web site or the services provided therein in the event we are unable to obtain or verify to our satisfaction the information which we request under this section.

**Other** : We may collect the Personal Identifiable Information you provide about yourself when you contact us; and Personal Identifiable Information you provide about yourself on your user profile, or anywhere else on the Site.

You can choose not to provide us with certain Personal Identifiable Information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of all of the Services.

**B. Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

From time to time, we may also ask you to provide us with non-personally identifiable information, that is, data that is not intended to allow us to identify you personally, such as your first name, birthday or postal code. This information may be aggregated and used for our internal purposes or for creating reports for third-party advertisers and partners, or otherwise shared with third parties for any lawful purpose, without your permission. No third party is intended to be able to know who you are as a result of the use of this information.

When you register to use the Site, CSGOShop may receive non-personally identifiable information from, such as your Valve user name.

If you purchase, sell products or services, or list a product or service for sale using the Services, we may receive from Valve or from PayPal, non-personally identifiable information including, but not limited to, your Valve user name, IP address, browser fingerprints, browser version, and operating system version.

We also may automatically collect Site usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of users to the Site and/or Services, pages visited and similar data. This data is used in the aggregate, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that is intended to identify you personally. Aggregate information generally is collected through the use of cookies and web beacons as discussed below. This aggregate information helps CSGOShop determine general usage patterns and modify the Site in order to improve your experience. This type of aggregate information may be shared with third parties at any time.

**C. Passive Gathering of Information Electronically**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Site or the Services. CSGOShop and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie and web beacon information, and the page you requested. CSGOShop uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the Site and the Services.

**_II. HOW WE USE INFORMATION_**

When you provide us with your information, we may use such information for a number of purposes, including:

  * To facilitate communication between CSGOShop and you including, without limitation, responding to your questions or comments, sending e-mails concerning our products and services, or to contact you for feedback regarding us, our advertisers or our business partners;
  * To process payments, verify payments or the authenticity of the payment information provided, or provide products or services to you and for CSGOShop marketing and promotional activities;
  * To provide a report to business partners that tells them who responded to a particular offer or to facilitate the fulfilment of an order that you have made with an advertiser or business partner;
  * To provide you with important functionality changes to the Site, new Services and special offers from CSGOShop and reputable third parties that we think you will find valuable;
  * To customize, analyze, adjust and improve the Site to meet our or our business partners' needs and expectations;
  * To enforce our agreements with you, prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities, for other legally permissible purposes and generally to ensure that we comply with applicable laws; and/or
  * To contact you by e-mail with respect to your use of the Site or Services, or with respect to marketing and promotions, if you have opted to be contacted by CSGOShop by e-mail.

**_III. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES_**

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your Personal Identifiable Information to anyone and that we will share your Personal Identifiable Information only as described below.

**A. Fulfilment of Services**

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include, but are not limited to, companies and individuals who: (i) process payments; (ii) conduct surveys or promotional activities; (iii) deliver products or services; (iv) verify payments or payment information; or (v) provide customer support, web hosting, internet service, and data analysis. Such third parties may be provided with access to information needed to perform their functions but may not use such information for any other purpose.

**B. Protection of CSGOShop and Others**

We may release Personal Identifiable Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of CSGOShop, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**C. Business Transfers**

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if CSGOShop, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets transferred.

**D. CSGOShop Personnel**

CSGOShop personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to Personal Identifiable Information, where such access is necessary in the normal course of CSGOShop’s business.

**_IV. IMPORTANT DISCLOSURES, PRACTICES AND CONTACT INFORMATION_**

**A. Third Party Links**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by web sites linked to or from our Site or Services, nor for the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link or go from our Site to another web site, including those sites that have a link on our Site, you are subject to that other web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding to interact with such other website.

**B. Data Security**

We maintain a variety of commercially reasonable safeguards designed to protect your Personal Identifiable Information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, we use industry accepted tools and techniques to protect against unauthorized access to our systems.

You should be aware, however, that CSGOShop has no control over the security of other web sites on the Internet that you might visit, even where such other site is linked to our Site. If you share your computer or use a computer that is accessed by the general public, remember to sign off and close your browser window when you have finished your session. This will help to ensure that others cannot access your information.

We want you to feel confident using the Site. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take commercially reasonable steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your information, searches or other communications always will remain secure. In the event of a breach of the confidentiality or security of your information, we will notify you if reasonably possible and as reasonably necessary so that you can take appropriate protective steps. We may notify you under such circumstances using the e-mail address(es) we have on record for you. You should also take care with how you handle and disclose your information.

**C. Children**

You must be 13 years and older to use the Site. As a result, CSGOShop does not intentionally collect information about children under the age of 13. If we learn that CSGOShop has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We require that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive a parent’s or guardian’s permission before using CSGOShop or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet. If you are under the age of 18, you warrant that you have the express permission of your parent or legal guardian to use the Site and to give information about yourself to the Site. If you are a parent or legal guardian and have authorised a minor to use the Site and Services, you agree that you are responsible for the online conduct of the minor, and for the consequences of any misuse of the Site and/or Services by the minor.

**D. No Rights of Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties.

**E. Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about CSGOShop generally, this Privacy Policy or the Site, please feel free to contact us by sending an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7e0d0b0e0e110c0a3e1d0d19110d16110e501d1113).
